T. J. Anderson Papers MS006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Compositions by T.J. Anderson, 1956 -- 2004; 1975 -- 2004; MS006.003; 18.25 Linear Feet
  - Soldier boy, soldier, 1982; MS006.003.032.00025 (Box 32)
    Correspondence and articles. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-23#00001.
  - A song for Elma Lewis, 2004; MS006.003.032.00026 (Box 32)
    Lyrics and notes from T. J. Anderson. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-024#00005.
  - The suit, 1998; MS006.003.032.00027 (Box 32)
    Lyrics. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-025#00002.
  - Thomas Jefferson's minstrels, 1982; MS006.003.032.00028 (Box 32)
    Articles, correspondence, and text. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-025#00007.
  - Thomas Jefferson's minstrels, 1982; MS006.003.032.00029 (Box 32)
    Correspondence and articles. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-025#00007.
  - Thomas Jefferson's minstrels, 1982; MS006.003.032.00030 (Box 32)
    Research material, correspondence, and articles. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-025#00007.
  - Treemonisha [Bolcom orchestration], 1982; MS006.003.032.00031 (Box 32)
    [1 of 4] Notes and copy of score. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha [Bolcom orchestration], 1982; MS006.003.032.00032 (Box 32)
    [2 of 4] Notes and copy of score. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha [Bolcom orchestration], 1982; MS006.003.032.00033 (Box 32)
    [3 of 4] Notes and copy of score. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha [Bolcom orchestration], 1982; MS006.003.032.00034 (Box 32)
    [4 of 4] Notes and copy of score. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.032.00035 (Box 32)
    Newspaper articles. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.032.00036 (Box 32)
    Correspondence. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.032.00037 (Box 32)
    Correspondence, research material, and the libretto. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.032.00038 (Box 32)
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.032.00039 (Box 32)
    Correspondence, research materials, and articles. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/003-028#00001.
  - Treemonisha, 1982; MS006.003.032.00040 (Box 32)
    Correspondence, research materials, and articles. Associated materials can be found at MS006/003-027#00001 and MS006/028#00001.
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.032.00041 (Box 32)
    Libretto. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-030#00001 and MS006/003-031#00001.
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.032.00042 (Box 32)
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.032.00043 (Box 32)
  - Walker, 1992; MS006.003.032.00044 (Box 32)
    Research material, program, and the libretto. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-030#00001 and MS006/003-031#00001.
  - What time is it?, 1986; MS006.003.032.00045 (Box 32)
    Correspondence. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-031#00005.
  - Words my mother taught me, 2000; MS006.003.032.00046 (Box 32)
    Source material. Associated material can be found at MS006/003-031#00006.
- Compositions by other composers, 1955 -- 2004; 1970 -- 1999; MS006.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series consists of printed music scores collected or given to T.J. Anderson by other composers. Many of these scores were composed in honor of T. J. Anderson's 60th birthday. T. J. Anderson does not own the copyright which continues to reside with the original composer
  This series is arranged alphabetically by composer's last name.
  - Baker, David: Le chat qui peche; Two improvisations, 1974; MS006.004.033.00001 (Box 33)
  - Berio, Luciano: Nones, 1955; MS006.004.033.00002 (Box 33)
  - Berlioz, Hector: Requiem, 1955; MS006.004.033.00003 (Box 33)
  - Bolcom, William: Birthday piece, 1989; MS006.004.033.00004 (Box 33)
  - Boroff, Edith: A drag and a rag, 1980; MS006.004.033.00005 (Box 33)
  - Carduso, Lindembergue: Procissao das carpideiras, 1969; MS006.004.033.00006 (Box 33)
  - Da Costa, Noel: In the landscape of spring; Longevity, 1977; MS006.004.033.00007 (Box 33)
  - David, Avram: Blues/Raga, 1988; MS006.004.033.00008 (Box 33)
  - DeVoto, Mark: Intrada, 1988; MS006.004.033.00009 (Box 33)
  - Englemann, Hans Ulrich: Tastenstuck, 1991 -- 1993; MS006.004.033.00010 (Box 33)
  - Hyston, Scott: Intensity II, 1975; MS006.004.033.00011 (Box 33)
  - Lindgren, Erik: 888; String Quartet #2, 1989 -- 2004; MS006.004.033.00012 (Box 33)
  - Lindroth, Scott: Spin cycle, 2001; MS006.004.033.00013 (Box 33)
  - McDonald, John: Initials, 1998; MS006.004.033.00014 (Box 33)
  - McNeil, Genna Rae: When visited by storms, 1996; MS006.004.033.00015 (Box 33)
  - Oboe, Thomas: Concerto for two pianos and chamber orchestra; Happy birthday to T.J., 1983 -- 1988; MS006.004.033.00016 (Box 33)
  - Penderecki, Krzysztof: Passio et mors Domini nostri Jesu Christi secundum lucam, 1967; MS006.004.033.00017 (Box 33)
  - Pisaro, Michael: Hamm's reminiscence; A little bit of rhythm and soul; Resonance, 1985 -- 2000; MS006.004.034.00001 (Box 34)
    This date is approximate.
  - Santos, Henry: Leola, 1989; MS006.004.034.00002 (Box 34)
  - Singleton, Alvin: Argoru VII, 1994; MS006.004.034.00003 (Box 34)
  - Smith, Hale: Meditations in passage; A ternion of season, 1980 -- 1996; MS006.004.034.00004 (Box 34)
  - Sur, Donald: Slavery documents, 1990; MS006.004.034.00005 (Box 34)
  - Tanner, Robert: Duo momentum; Fanfare fo Dr. King; Ornaments; Romance, 1996 -- 2004; MS006.004.034.00006 (Box 34)
  - Taylor, Billy: Make a joyful noise, 1980; MS006.004.034.00007 (Box 34)
  - Weston, Trevor: Ashes; Evening songs; The gentlest thing; Mat'at musings, 1999 -- 2004; MS006.004.034.00008 (Box 34)
  - Williams, James: Four songs for cello and piano, 1980; MS006.004.034.00009 (Box 34)
  - Wilson, Olly: Spiritsong, 1973; MS006.004.034.00010 (Box 34)
  - Orchestral masterpiece collections of Korean contemporary composers, 1997; MS006.004.034.00011 (Box 34)
  - Unknown, 1980; MS006.004.034.00012 (Box 34)
- Recordings by other composers, 1954 -- 2005; MS006.005; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of audio recordings collected or given to T.J. Anderson by other composers. Audio recordings include audiocassettes, compact disks, and 8 inch sound discs. T. J. Anderson does not own the copyright which continues to reside with the original composer/performer.
  - 2001 live birds, 2004; MS006.005.035.00001; Birdsongs of the Mesozoic (Case 35)
  - Another Cape Cod summer (this year), 1982; MS006.005.035.00002; The Space Negros (Case 35)
    phonograph record
  - Argoru VII, 1994; MS006.005.035.00003; Singleton, Alvin (Case 35)
    audiocassette
  - Blueskonzert; Umoja-each one of us counts, 1995 -- 1996; MS006.005.035.00004; Singleton, Alvin (Case 35)
  - Bob Oaks morning edition (NPR/WBUR) Donal Fox: Monk and Bach (10/11/00), 2000; MS006.005.035.00005; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Chamber operas, 2005; MS006.005.035.00006; Banfield, William (Case 35)
  - Compositions by Trevor Weston, 1995; MS006.005.035.00007; Weston, Trevor (Case 35)
  - Donal Fox exploring Monk and Bach, part II, 2000; MS006.005.035.00008; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Donal Fox with BBC host Judy Sallow; the connection on NPR, 2001; MS006.005.035.00009; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Donal Fox/Richmond Symphony Anthony Kelley's "Africamerica", 1999; MS006.005.035.00010; Kelley, Anthony; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Essays of note, 2004; MS006.005.035.00011; Banfield, William (Case 35)
  - For hymn, 2003; MS006.005.035.00012; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
    CD one.
  - For hymn, 2003; MS006.005.035.00013; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
    CD two.
  - Forests: a book of hours, 1999; MS006.005.035.00014; Quin, Douglas (Case 35)
  - Fr[Act(u)al(s)], 2004; MS006.005.035.00015; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
  - Go commercial, 1980; MS006.005.035.00016; The Space Negros (Case 35)
  - Go to Russia/go to hell, 1981; MS006.005.035.00017; The Space Negros (Case 35)
  - Hale Smith, 1995; MS006.005.035.00018; Smith, Hale (Case 35)
    This date is appoximate.
  - Have a lousy christmas, 1990; MS006.005.035.00019; The Space Negros (Case 35)
  - Hold on: symp. no. 3, 1999; MS006.005.035.00020; Wilson, Olly (Case 35)
  - The intersection of concert and vernacular traditions, 2005; MS006.005.035.00021; Dawson, William Levi (Case 35)
  - Inventions in blue II, 2002; MS006.005.035.00022; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - The iridium controversy, 2003; MS006.005.035.00023; Birdsongs of the Mesozoic (Case 35)
  - John McDonald: inventious network op. 382, 2002; MS006.005.035.00024; McDonald, John (Case 35)
  - M B Tolson at Library of Congress, 1965; MS006.005.035.00025; Tolson, Melvin B. (Case 35)
  - Mass for the holy year, 2000; MS006.005.035.00026; Lee, Thomas Oboe (Case 35)
  - Mining our bid'ness, 2002; MS006.005.035.00027; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
  - Minstral man, 2004; MS006.005.035.00028; Thomas, Marco (Case 35)
  - More works, 2002 -- 2003; MS006.005.035.00029; Banfield, William (Case 35)
  - Music composition, 1998; MS006.005.035.00030; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
  - Music for hammers and sticks, 2004; MS006.005.035.00031; Shapiro, Alex (Case 35)
  - Music of Gary Powell Nash, 1992; MS006.005.035.00032; Nash, Gary Powell (Case 35)
  - My true identity (an exerpt from who it is), 1999; MS006.005.035.00033; Kirshner, Andy (Case 35)
  - Odysseus reading side 1 and 2, 1997; MS006.005.035.00034; Tasner, Clifford J. (Case 35)
  - Odysseus reading side 3, 1997; MS006.005.035.00035; Tasner, Clifford J. (Case 35)
  - Oil on linen, 1992; MS006.005.035.00036; Lindgren, Erik (Case 35)
  - Oral moses, 2003; MS006.005.035.00037; Birdsongs of the Mesozoic (Case 35)
  - Orchestral works, 1991-1999, 2000; MS006.005.035.00038; Kelley, Anthony (Case 35)
  - Orchestral/chamber jazz works, 2005; MS006.005.035.00039; Banfield, William (Case 35)
  - Pavane Zortzico, 1997; MS006.005.035.00040; DeVoto, Mark (Case 35)
  - Piano piece and string quartet II, 1992 -- 1993; MS006.005.035.00041; DeVoto, Mark (Case 35)
  - Pieces of dreams, 1998; MS006.005.035.00042; Tassone, Pasquale (Case 35)
  - Recent works, 1986 -- 1999; MS006.005.035.00043; DeVoto, Mark (Case 35)
  - Say you have this ball of meaning, 2005; MS006.005.035.00044; Singleton, Alvin (Case 35)
  - Scarlatto jazz suite demo disc no. 1, 2003; MS006.005.035.00045; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Scarlatti jazz suite demo disc no. 2, 2003; MS006.005.035.00046; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Selections, 1998; MS006.005.035.00047; Tassone, Pasquale (Case 35)
  - Sfp, 2003; MS006.005.035.00048; Kelley, Anthony (Case 35)
  - Society of black composers, 1967; MS006.005.035.00049; Bell, Charles (Case 35)
  - Somehow we can, 2002; MS006.005.035.00050; Singleton, Alvin (Case 35)
  - Sound window(s) V February 6, 2004; MS006.005.035.00051; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
  - Sound window(s) V February 7, 2004; MS006.005.035.00052; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
  - Spin cycle, 2001; MS006.005.035.00053; Lindroth, Scott (Case 35)
  - Striking balance, 2005; MS006.005.035.00055; Banfield, William (Case 35)
  - String quartet #2, 2004; MS006.005.035.00056; Lindgren, Erik (Case 35)
  - String quartet on b-flat, 1993; MS006.005.035.00057; Lee, Thomas Oboe (Case 35)
  - Tastenstuck, 1993; MS006.005.035.00058; Englemann, Hans Ulrich (Case 35)
  - This thread, 2004; MS006.005.035.00059; Scearce, J. Mark (Case 35)
  - Thomas Oboe Lee, 1998 -- 2000; MS006.005.035.00060; Lee, Thomas Oboe (Case 35)
  - Toccata on Bach, 2001; MS006.005.035.00061; Fox, Donal (Case 35)
  - Ultan: tribute concert, 1994; MS006.005.035.00062; Ultan, Lloyd (Case 35)
  - Untitled, 1997; MS006.005.035.00063; Forrest, Leon; Terkel, Studs (Case 35)
  - Urban classical the music of Ed Bland, 1994; MS006.005.035.00064; Bland, Ed (Case 35)
  - Videmus honors Vivian Taylor, 1998; MS006.005.035.00065; Videmus (Case 35)
    Tape 1.
  - Videmus honors Vivian Taylor, 1998; MS006.005.035.00066; Videmus (Case 35)
    Tape 2.
  - W. O. Smith tunes, 1985; MS006.005.035.00067; Smith, W. O. (Case 35)
  - Walker: lilacs for voice and orchestra, 1996; MS006.005.035.00068; Walker, George (Case 35)
  - Walking through songs, 2000; MS006.005.035.00069; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
  - The wall, 1954; MS006.005.035.00070; Englemann, Hans Ulrich (Case 35)
    Work is originally entitled Die Mauer.
  - Weston works 2004, MS006.005.035.00071; Weston, Trevor (Case 35)
  - Weston works, 2000; MS006.005.035.00072; Weston, Trevor (Case 35)
  - Weston works, 2000; MS006.005.035.00073; Weston, Trevor (Case 35)
  - With respect to...musical comments and reflections on the work of Wassily Kandinsky, 2001; MS006.005.035.00074; Kandinsky, Wassily; Thomas, Carei F. (Case 35)
- Additional accessions, 1928 -- 2012; 1928 -- 2010; MS006.006; 46.8 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series comprises unprocessed accessions, including scores, composition files, programs, audiovisual materials, news clippings, awards, and administration, teaching, and personal files, circa 1928-2010.
  This series includes many printed scores as well as original manuscripts. Also included is a script for "The Reincarnated Beethoven" with composition notes. There are programs for Anderson's performances as well as performances by other musicians. Audiovisual materials include CD, audiocassette, and audio reel recordings. Of particular note are The HistoryMakers oral history interview (CD), 2012, and audio recordings (CD) from the world premiere performance of "Boogie Woogie Concertante" at Anderson's 75th birthday celebration with the Harvard University Wind Ensemble, December 6, 2003. This series also includes an audio reel recording of "Spirit Songs, Part II" performed at Oberlin College, 1981, and a VHS recording of "Slip Knot: An Opera in Two Acts," 2003.
  Awards include a Doctor of Fine Arts diploma from Northwestern University, 2002 (honorary degree); a Doctor of Music diploma from Bates College, 2005 (honorary degree) and photographs of commencement; a Doctor of Music diploma from Tufts University, 2007 (honorary degree); photographs of a Distinguished Alumni Award ceremony at University of Iowa, 2006; awards from the Massachusetts Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1981, and College of the Holy Cross, 1983; and plaques awarded by West Virginia State College, 1984 and 1995.
  Also of interest are records related to the Afro-American Music Workshop and the production of the opera "Treemonisha" at Morehouse College, 1972, and an untitled manuscript for a book project with Leon Forrest, circa 1989.
  Personal files include weekly planners, 1970-1987; a journal, 1987; an album of letters, compositions, and photographs presented to T. J. Anderson on his 75th birthday, August 17, 2003; a drawing and poem presented to T. J. Anderson on his 75th birthday by his granddaughter Yasmine, August 17, 2003; "River to Cross" book of poetry by T. J. Anderson III, 2009; and "Poems by Anita T. Anderson."
  This series is not arranged.
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - Awards, photos, folders, and posters, MS006.006.036 (Box data_value_missing_ebddb53e3857e381cf520bde37a1be68, Box 36)
  - Awards, photos, folders, and posters, MS006.006.037 (Box data_value_missing_ebddb53e3857e381cf520bde37a1be68, Box 37)
  - Awards, photos, folders, and posters, MS006.006.038 (Box data_value_missing_b2bc4f994aff7a2b3ca489382322ae6e, Box 38)
  - Autographed scores, manuscripts, photos, and audio materials, MS006.006.039 (Box data_value_missing_a5ec3a555c026332a8cef46bbbde1023, Box 39)
  - Autographed scores, manuscripts, photos, and audio materials, MS006.006.040 (Box data_value_missing_ebddb53e3857e381cf520bde37a1be68, Box 40)
  - Autographed scores, manuscripts, photos, and audio materials, MS006.006.041 (Box data_value_missing_ebddb53e3857e381cf520bde37a1be68, Box 41)
  - Library, audiovisual materials, and artifacts, 1990 -- 2010; MS006.006.042 (Box data_value_missing_21e5e14503df9d849b6df26d1aed0d01, Box 42)
    Books on music theory and African American culture and literature; audio cassettes and CDS; VHS recording of Slip Knot: An Opera in Two Acts, 2003; American Academy of Arts and Letters proceedings and group photograph, 2006; script for Walker: A Chamber Opera; programs; conducting batons; and National Humanities Center t-shirt, with group photograph of Fellows including T.J. Anderson, 1996.
  - Honorary degrees and awards, 1979 -- 2010; MS006.006.043 (Box data_value_missing_ebddb53e3857e381cf520bde37a1be68, Box 43)
    Doctor of Fine Arts diploma from Northwestern University, 2002 (honorary degree); Doctor of Music diploma from Bates College, 2005 (honorary degree) and photographs of commencement; Doctor of Music diploma from Tufts University, 2007 (honorary degree); photographs of Distinguished Alumni Award ceremony at University of Iowa, 2006; collectible cancelled stamps and news clipping commemorating Pope John Paul II's visit to Boston, 1979; and "So you want to write an opera" lecture given to Tufts alumni, 1982.
  - Correspondence, teaching, and administration files, 1972 -- 2003; MS006.006.044 (Box data_value_missing_21e5e14503df9d849b6df26d1aed0d01, Box 44)
    Correspondence related to teaching, composition, and performance, circa 1999-2003; teaching materials and administrative records; essays by students and colleagues; programs; records related to the Afro-American Music Workshop and the production of the opera "Treemonisha" at Morehouse College, 1972; "Game Play" score, 2002; and awards from the Massachusetts Council on the Arts and Humanities, 1981, and College of the Holy Cross, 1983.
  - Personal papers, programs, and scores, 1960 -- 2003; MS006.006.045 (Box data_value_missing_21e5e14503df9d849b6df26d1aed0d01, Box 45)
    Personal papers and news clippings, circa 1960-1980; weekly planners, 1970-1987; programs and photographs, circa 1970-2003; "A Musical Kaddish 'In Sea' for John Zimarowski" score, 1995; "The Suit" score, 1999; "Game Play" score, 2001; "Boogie Woogie Concertante" score, 2003; and plaques awarded by West Virginia State College, 1984 and 1995.
  - Scores, audiovisual materials, and 75th birthday album, 1970 -- 2010; MS006.006.046 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 46)
    "The Reincarnated Beethoven" script with composition notes; "Tuftonia's Call and Response" score, 2007; "Shouts (forty improvisations for Eva-Maria)" score, 1997; "The Wedding Party" score, 2008; "In Front of My Eyes: An Obama Celebration" score, 2010; "A Musical Kaddish 'In Sea' for John Zimarowski" score, 1995; "Cornerstones" score; "Fragments" score, 2006; "Slip Knot" score, 2000; "Spirit Songs" score,1993; "Aurelia, In Memoriam" score, 1999; "Boogie Woogie Fantasy" score,1997; "This House" score (original), 1971; "What Ever Happened to the Big Bands?" score, 1991; "Dear John, Dear Coltrane" score (original), 1989; "Game Play" score, 2001; "Boogie Woogie Concertante" score, 2003; "Watermelon" score, 1971; "Bridging and Branching" score, 1986; "Intermezzi" score, 1983; "Echoes"score, 1991; album of letters, compositions, and photographs presented to T.J. Anderson on his 75th birthday, August 17, 2003; drawing and poem presented to T.J. Anderson on his 75th birthday by his granddaughter Yasmine, August 17, 2003; "River to Cross" book of poetry by T.J. Anderson III, 2009; "Poems by Anita T. Anderson;" and audio cassettes and CDs.
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.047 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 47)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.048 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 48)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.049 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 49)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.050 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 50)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.051 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 51)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.052 (Box data_value_missing_af2f8a36339687f6bcf8e95108dafac0, Box 52)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.053 (Box data_value_missing_c9b2bed4eda2f2ce0eae7340ee51de4f, Box 53)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.054 (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 54)
  - Composition, administration, and personal files, and oral history interview, 1981 -- 2012; MS006.006.055 (Box data_value_missing_c9b2bed4eda2f2ce0eae7340ee51de4f, Box 55)
    Composition, administration, and personal files, circa 1990-1995. Also included are an audio reel recording of "Spirit Songs, Part II" performed at Oberlin College, 1981, audio cassettes, and The HistoryMakers oral history interview on CD, 2012.
  - Composition, administration, and personal files, 1972 -- 2010; MS006.006.056 (Box data_value_missing_664e716b7dc632d70b00a824c64a3277, Box 56)
    Composition, administration, and personal files, circa 1990-2008; records related to the Afro-American Music Workshop at Morehouse College, 1972; and records related to Anderson's service to the American Academy of Arts and Letters, 2006-2008.
  - Correspondence, awards, audiovisual materials, and programs, 1980 -- 2010; MS006.006.057 (Box data_value_missing_664e716b7dc632d70b00a824c64a3277, Box 57)
    75 years from the date of creation.
    Untitled manuscript for book project with Leon Forrest, circa 1989; correspondence; personal journal, 1987; programs; news clippings; scores written by composers other than Anderson; audio recordings (CD) by other musicians; program and audio recordings (CD) from the performance of Boogie Woogie Concertante at Anderson's 75th birthday celebration with the Harvard University Wind Ensemble, December 6, 2003; birthday cards; and records related to the "Wings Over Jordan" documentary project, 2006.
  - Oversize scores and audiovisual materials, MS006.006.058 (Box data_value_missing_c9b2bed4eda2f2ce0eae7340ee51de4f, Box 58)
  - Oversize scores and audiovisual materials, MS006.006.059 (Box data_value_missing_a5ec3a555c026332a8cef46bbbde1023, Box 59)
  - Files, correspondence, audiovisual materials, MS006.006.060 (Box data_value_missing_664e716b7dc632d70b00a824c64a3277, Box 60)
  - Correspondence, scores, awards, audiovisual materials, and programs, MS006.006.061 (Box data_value_missing_1550fbfd7e0c0282e8bf11ebd31a2d85, Box 61)
  - Correspondence, Black Music Caucus, and scores, MS006.006.062 (Box data_value_missing_1550fbfd7e0c0282e8bf11ebd31a2d85, Box 62)
  - Scores, MS006.006.063 (Box data_value_missing_1550fbfd7e0c0282e8bf11ebd31a2d85, Box 63)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.064 (Box data_value_missing_c9b2bed4eda2f2ce0eae7340ee51de4f, Box 64)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.065 (Box data_value_missing_c9b2bed4eda2f2ce0eae7340ee51de4f, Box 65)
  - Oversize scores, MS006.006.066 (Box data_value_missing_c9b2bed4eda2f2ce0eae7340ee51de4f, Box 66)
  - Composition, administration, and personal files, MS006.006.067 (Box data_value_missing_79e9098d3746ded5a06fc72e2d55ac1a, Box 67)
  - Scores, reels, letters, and Sam Bruskin, MS006.006.068 (Box data_value_missing_79e9098d3746ded5a06fc72e2d55ac1a, Box 68)
  - Audiotapes, books, and files, MS006.006.069 (Box data_value_missing_5366765388057e82f009faf7fe822c6b, Box 69)
  - Books, MS006.006.070 (Box data_value_missing_5366765388057e82f009faf7fe822c6b, Box 70)
  - Tufts University Department of Music 100th Celebration Concert, 1995-02-24; MS006.006.071; 1 Digital Object(s); 605 Megabytes (Box data_value_missing_bfc0175763a9ea7d44b13bcf562ece38, Box 71)
  - Audio and video tapes, MS006.006.072 (Box data_value_missing_79e9098d3746ded5a06fc72e2d55ac1a, Box 72)